<resources>
    <string name="app_name">mad.g7.nak.ex1</string>
    <string name="hello_en">Hello World</string>
    <string name="string1">Random String 1</string>
    <string name="string2">Random String 2</string>
    <string name="string3">Random String 3</string>
    <string name="newspaper">Wright has been a nurse for more than 20 years in Fort Myers, Fla. She began working in hospitals as a teenage candy striper in Upstate New York, progressing through an associate’s degree in nursing, then a bachelor’s, then a master’s, then finally a doctorate of nursing practice in 2013. Wright has always told patients she’s a nurse practitioner, she says. She doesn’t flaunt her doctorate or try to mislead patients into thinking she has an MD.

Still, when Florida lawmakers began considering a bill that would have prevented her from using her title, Wright was taken aback.

“I’ve never abused or borne witness to anyone abusing their title,” she said. “It’s singling people out, creating a bad atmosphere through legislation for the actions of a few.”

The Florida bill would have prevented non-physicians from using several titles such as doctor of medicine, physician, medical resident and hospitalist. (Gov. Ron DeSantis vetoed it in June.) A near-identical measure became law in Georgia this year and Indiana in 2022. California ordered a nurse practitioner to pay nearly $20,000 for advertising herself as “Doctor Sarah,” based on a law that several nurses are now challenging.

Florida and Georgia are two of many states contending with how much independence to give nurse practitioners and other medical professionals. It’s a question that has become emotional for many medical providers and time-consuming for many state and federal groups lobbying on their behalf.</string>
    <string name="scrolltext">Kotlin is a statically typed,
                 general-purpose programming language developed
                 by JetBrains, that has built world-class IDEs
                 like IntelliJ IDEA, PhpStorm, Appcode, etc.
                 It was first introduced by JetBrains in 2011
                 and a new language for the JVM. Kotlin is
                 object-oriented language, and a “better language”
                 than Java, but still be fully interoperable
                 with Java code. Kotlin is sponsored by Google,
                 announced as one of the official languages for
                 Android Development in 2017.
                 Advantages of Kotlin language:
                 Easy to learn – Basic is almost similar to java.
                 If anybody worked in java then easily understand
                 in no time. Kotlin is multi-platform – Kotlin is
                 supported by all IDEs of java so you can write
                 your program and execute them on any machine
                 which supports JVM. It’s much safer than Java.
                 It allows using the Java frameworks and libraries
                 in your new Kotlin projects by using advanced
                 frameworks without any need to change the whole
                 project in Java. Kotlin programming language,
                 including the compiler, libraries and all the
                 tooling is completely free and open source and
                 available on github. Here is the link for
                 Github https://github.com/JetBrains/kotlin
                 Applications of Kotlin language:
                 You can use Kotlin to build Android Application.
                 Kotlin can also compile to JavaScript, and making
                 it available for the frontend. It is also designed
                 to work well for web development and server-side
                 development.Kotlin is a statically typed, general-purpose
                 programming language developed by JetBrains that
                 has built world-class IDEs like IntelliJ IDEA,
                 PhpStorm, Appcode, etc. It was first introduced
                 by JetBrains in 2011.Kotlin is object-oriented
                 language and a better language than Java, but still
                 be fully interoperable with Java code. A constructor
                 is a special member function that is invoked when
                 an object of the class is created primarily to initialize
                 variables or properties. A class needs to have a constructor
                 and if we do not declare a constructor, then the compiler
                 generates a default constructor.
                 Kotlin has two types of constructors –
                 Primary Constructor
                 Secondary Constructor
                 A class in Kotlin can have at most one primary
                 constructor, and one or more secondary constructors.
                 The primary constructor
                 initializes the class, while the secondary
                 constructor is used
                 to initialize the class and introduce some extra logic.
                 Explanation:
                 When we create the object add for the class then
                 the values 5 and 6
                 passes to the constructor. The constructor
                 parameters a and b
                 initialize with the parameters 5 and 6 respectively.
                 The local variable c contains the sum of variables.
                 In the main, we access the property of
                 constructor using ${add.c}.
                 Explanation:
                 Here, we have initialized the constructor
                 parameters with some
                 default values emp_id = 100 and emp_name = “abc”.
                 When the object emp is created we passed the values for
                 both the parameters so it prints those values.
                 But, at the time of object emp2 creation,
                 we have not passed
                 the emp_name so initializer block uses
                 the default values and
                 print to the standard output.
        Kotlin is a statically typed,
                 general-purpose programming language developed
                 by JetBrains, that has built world-class IDEs
                 like IntelliJ IDEA, PhpStorm, Appcode, etc.
                 It was first introduced by JetBrains in 2011
                 and a new language for the JVM. Kotlin is
                 object-oriented language, and a “better language”
                 than Java, but still be fully interoperable
                 with Java code. Kotlin is sponsored by Google,
                 announced as one of the official languages for
                 Android Development in 2017.
                 Advantages of Kotlin language:
                 Easy to learn – Basic is almost similar to java.
                 If anybody worked in java then easily understand
                 in no time. Kotlin is multi-platform – Kotlin is
                 supported by all IDEs of java so you can write
                 your program and execute them on any machine
                 which supports JVM. It’s much safer than Java.
                 It allows using the Java frameworks and libraries
                 in your new Kotlin projects by using advanced
                 frameworks without any need to change the whole
                 project in Java. Kotlin programming language,
                 including the compiler, libraries and all the
                 tooling is completely free and open source and
                 available on github. Here is the link for
                 Github https://github.com/JetBrains/kotlin
                 Applications of Kotlin language:
                 You can use Kotlin to build Android Application.
                 Kotlin can also compile to JavaScript, and making
                 it available for the frontend. It is also designed
                 to work well for web development and server-side
                 development.Kotlin is a statically typed, general-purpose
                 programming language developed by JetBrains that
                 has built world-class IDEs like IntelliJ IDEA,
                 PhpStorm, Appcode, etc. It was first introduced
                 by JetBrains in 2011.Kotlin is object-oriented
                 language and a better language than Java, but still
                 be fully interoperable with Java code. A constructor
                 is a special member function that is invoked when
                 an object of the class is created primarily to initialize
                 variables or properties. A class needs to have a constructor
                 and if we do not declare a constructor, then the compiler
                 generates a default constructor.
                 Kotlin has two types of constructors –
                 Primary Constructor
                 Secondary Constructor
                 A class in Kotlin can have at most one primary
                 constructor, and one or more secondary constructors.
                 The primary constructor
                 initializes the class, while the secondary
                 constructor is used
                 to initialize the class and introduce some extra logic.
                 Explanation:
                 When we create the object add for the class then
                 the values 5 and 6
                 passes to the constructor. The constructor
                 parameters a and b
                 initialize with the parameters 5 and 6 respectively.
                 The local variable c contains the sum of variables.
                 In the main, we access the property of
                 constructor using ${add.c}.
                 Explanation:
                 Here, we have initialized the constructor
                 parameters with some
                 default values emp_id = 100 and emp_name = “abc”.
                 When the object emp is created we passed the values for
                 both the parameters so it prints those values.
                 But, at the time of object emp2 creation,
                 we have not passed
                 the emp_name so initializer block uses
                 the default values and
                 print to the standard output.

    </string>
</resources>